

ENGLESH REUBEN-HEKE

• DETAILS •

Brisbane, 4035 0478070401 reubenheke21@gmail.com

LINKS

<u>Linkedin</u>

SquareSpace Blog Website

Portfolio of webpages

Shopify Droppshipping Store

° SKILLS °

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

Python

C# & .NET

SquareSpace

Shopify

PROFILE

Enthusiastic self-taught Web Developer seeking to launch a career in building web applications, web pages, and services. My skills consist of programming languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, C# and .NET. I am familiar with Bootstrap, React, Node.js, RestAPI's, JSON, Agile, and Scrum methodologies. I bring with me 9+ years in customer service based roles with 2+ years within the Finance field.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Web Developer at Self Taught

December 2022 — Present

I am a very passionate Web Developer who is looking at starting a career in Web Development, I have found every way possible I can to upskill myself and learn things in my spare time to be competent in the role I wish to attain. To this day I have created 3 different web pages, 2 using Shopify as an E-commerce store, and 1 as a blog on Squarespace. I have completed and obtained certificates for:

- FreeCodeCamp Responsive Web Design
- Coursera's Python for Everybody
- Mimo's Python Course
- -Udemy's The Complete Web Developer

During the last 7 months, I have learned everything there is to know about running websites, uploading content, and creating aesthetically pleasing work to make sure that it's very user-friendly and inviting to my target audience.

Senior Home Loan Service Specialist at Commonwealth Bank, Brisbane

July 2021 — Present

- Demonstrate the ability to meet KPI's on a regular basis as discussed with my career coach.
- Typing skill of 59 WPM with 97% accuracy.
- Evaluating customers on their financial needs and objectives, ensuring all customers are compliant within the business's rules and regulations.
- Consistently volunteering within the company to voice my opinion and showcase ideas on how to make the business functionality more efficient.
- Promoted within the Direct Lending sector into Tier 2 which was dealing with more responsibility and handling more complex customer inquiries within 3 months of working for the business
- Showed further dedication for the business and was Promoted to Tier 3 which deals with Interest Only Applications. Broadened my knowledge for assessing applications and having difficult conversations with customers.
- Reviewed and processed individual loan and credit applications.

Junior Broker at Credit One Equipment Finance, Brisbane

September 2020 — June 2021

 Action all new leads at the start of the day and then within 5 minutes of receiving new ones.

- Data entry within the company CRM and obtaining all required information to ensure all customers objectives and requirements are met.
- Following all NCCP guidelines and ensuring all information entered is compliant.
- Obtained, verified, and compiled copies of loan applicants' credit histories, corporate financial statements, and other financial information.
- Excellent customer service skills, being able to negotiate with clients based on rate, loan term and repayments.

Customer Service Officer at Cash Train, Brisbane

February 2020 — September 2020

- Take inbound calls, handling all customer queries in a polite and timely manner.
- Ensuring all customer records are kept up to date.
- Making outbound calls to customers and negotiating with them to come to an agreement with the collections process.
- Assessing customers for Cash Train services and ensuring all information is collected and accurate.
- Running reports every day so to make sure that no new applications were missed, payments are going through correctly and discharging any customers who have paid off their loan.
- Assisting the branch manager with monthly KPI's and reaching targets every month

EDUCATION

High School Certificate, Bribie Island State High School, Bribie Island January 2010 — November 2012

Obtained High School Certificate and Graduated with an OP of 14.

■ REFERENCES

References available upon request